(Raj:)because there's a bumblebee
in my office.
(Leonard:)I saw it. It's big.
(Howard:)Anyway,
like I said in the e-mail,
(Howard:)this meeting's on Thursday.
(Howard:)Do you have any advice for us?
(Marty:)Well, I don't know much
about patent law.
But, uh, my advice is:
(Marty:)hear them out, offer as little
information as possible,
(Marty:)and whatever you do,
don't sign anything.
"Don't sign anything"?
That's your advice?
(Sheldon:)Okay, so, uh, if
during this meeting,
(Sheldon:)one of us were to, say,
complete an oil painting,
(Sheldon:)you'd recommend that
we leave that unsigned?
(Marty:)That's not what I meant.
(Sheldon:)That's what you said.
(Sheldon:)This must be how
you practice law
(Sheldon:)in Boca Raton, by saying
things you don't mean
(Sheldon:)and meaning things
you don't say.
(Marty:)Howard, why is he yelling at me?
All right, you
were on Jeopardy.
Allow me to Alex Trebek this and
put it in the form of a question:
Who has been a complete
waste of our time?
(Howard:)Marty, let me call you back.
(Leonard:)Someday, when I'm up
on murder charges,
(Leonard:)you'll be hearing from me.